verifyemailaddress.io 2015-03-27

# Privacy Policy - verifyemailaddress.io

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us using our contact form.

At verifyemailaddress.io we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by verifyemailaddress.io and how we use it.

## Data protection

verifyemailaddress.io warrants that:

  1. it will act only on instructions from the Customer in relation to the processing of any Personal Data performed by the Provider on behalf of the Customer; and
  2. it has in place appropriate security measures (both technical and organisational) against unlawful or unauthorised processing of Personal Data and against loss or corruption of Personal Data processed by the Provider on behalf of the Customer.

## Confidentiality

verifyemailaddress.io will:

  1. keep confidential and not disclose the Customer Confidential Information to any person save as expressly permitted by this policy;
  2. protect the Customer Confidential Information against unauthorised disclosure by using the same degree of care as it takes to preserve and safeguard its own confidential information of a similar nature, being at least a reasonable degree of care.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, verifyemailaddress.io makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site - usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services's analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

verifyemailaddress.io uses cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on verifyemailaddress.io.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site's visitors based upon their visit to verifyemailaddress.io and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

## Google Analytics

Users may opt out of Google Analytics ath the following URL - <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>.

### Cookies

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. [What Are Cookies?](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/what-are-cookies)

## Children's Information

We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. verifyemailaddress.io does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that verifyemailaddress.io has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

## Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

## Update

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Friday, January 23rd, 2015.

## Related

  * Please also see our Terms Of Service
